Contact

hasanghayas123@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/hassan-muhammad-ghayas-a565b1179 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills
Ionic Framework
ASP.NET Core
ASP.NET MVC

Hassan Muhammad Ghayas

Software Engineer at Urwasoft

Pakistan

Summary

Experienced Software Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the computer software industry. Skilled in WinForms, ADO.NET, Database Management System (DBMS), ASP.NET, and Ionic Framework. Strong engineering professional with a Bachelor of Science - BS focused in Computer Software Engineering from Usman Insitute of Technology.

Experience

Urwasoft

3 years 7 months

Software Engineer April 2020 - Present (1 year 10 months)

Karāchi, Sindh, Pakistan

Junior Software Engineer July 2018 - March 2020 (1 year 9 months) Karachi

CodeAesthetics

Intern

March 2018 - May 2018 (3 months)

Sindhi Muslim Society

Worked as intern in codeaesthtics for three months on different projects having different platforms which includes Xamarin, Ionic, Angular, .Net MVC.

Education

Usman Insitute of Technology

Bachelor of Science - BS, Computer Software Engineering (2015 - 2019)